<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CatalystNeuro at Cosyne 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-at-cosyne-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-at-cosyne-2024/</guid>
      <description>This year, CatalystNeuro had the incredible opportunity to be part of the Computational and Systems Neuroscience (Cosyne) 2024 conference, a cornerstone event where the brightest minds in neuroscience converge to explore cutting-edge research and methodologies. Our participation was marked by a fruitful tutorial, engaging discussions, and the invaluable chance to connect with fellow researchers and enthusiasts in the field.&#xA;Workshop on Data Conversion and Publishing One of the highlights of our participation was the workshop led by myself, along with Ryan Ly from Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatalystNeuro at the African Brain Data Science Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/bridging-continents-catalystneuro-at-the-african-brain-data-science-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/bridging-continents-catalystneuro-at-the-african-brain-data-science-academy/</guid>
      <description>At CatalystNeuro, we are passionate about fostering global collaborations that advance the frontiers of neuroscience research and education. Recently, we had the distinct opportunity to contribute to the African Brain Data Science Academy, an initiative under the African Brain Data Network aimed at enhancing data science skills across the continent.&#xA;The Importance of Global Collaboration in Neuroscience In the field of neuroscience, the challenges are as vast as the opportunities. Advancing our understanding of the brain requires not only sophisticated technology but also unparalleled collaboration across borders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatalystNeuro Company Retreat in Barcelona</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-company-retreat-in-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-company-retreat-in-barcelona/</guid>
      <description>Embracing Work and Play at Villa Mas Sant Jordi In the heart of the Costa Brava, just a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw from the bustling city of Barcelona and the serene beaches of the Mediterranean, CatalystNeuro recently found a perfect fusion of work and relaxation at Villa Mas Sant Jordi. Our annual company retreat was not only a chance to bond and brainstorm but also to immerse ourselves in the splendor of Spanish culture and nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillel Adesnik</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/hillel-adesnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/hillel-adesnik/</guid>
      <description>We developed ndx-patterend-ogen, an NWB extension for holographic patterned optogenetic stimulation as part of the MouseV1 U19 project. We used this extension in a custom conversion pipeline, mousev1-to-nwb, converting data from their Nature Neuroscience 2024 paper, &amp;ldquo;The logic of recurrent circuits in the primary visual cortex.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mission/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Solution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/software-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/software-solution/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work with Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work-with-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
