<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hillel Adesnik</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/hillel-adesnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/hillel-adesnik/</guid>
      <description>We developed ndx-patterend-ogen, an NWB extension for holographic patterned optogenetic stimulation as part of the MouseV1 U19 project. We used this extension in a custom conversion pipeline, mousev1-to-nwb, converting data from their Nature Neuroscience 2024 paper, &amp;ldquo;The logic of recurrent circuits in the primary visual cortex.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misha Ahrens</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/misha-ahrens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/misha-ahrens/</guid>
      <description>Working with Misha Ahrens&amp;rsquo; lab at Janelia, we developed ahrens-lab-to-nwb, an open repo to convert data from their custom optical physiology acquisition system to NWB. This pipeline was used to standardize and publish the data associated with their Cell 2019 paper, &amp;ldquo;Glia Accumulate Evidence that Actions Are Futile and Suppress Unsuccessful Behavior.&amp;rdquo; The NWB dataset is published on DANDI as DANDI:000350/0.221219.1506. The dataset contains 5.9 TB of optical physiology data from zebrafish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Axel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/richard-axel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/richard-axel/</guid>
      <description>Working with Richard Axel&amp;rsquo;s lab at Columbia University, we developed axel-lab-to-nwb, a pipelin for converting their whole-brain fly two photon neurophysiology to NWB.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Dombeck</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/daniel-dombeck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/daniel-dombeck/</guid>
      <description>We developed dombeck-lab-to-nwb, an open NWB conversion pipeline including fiber photometry, ScanImage two-photon microscopy, suite2p, video camera, and DeepLabCut data as well as behavioral metrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Higley</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/michael-higley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/michael-higley/</guid>
      <description>We developed higley-lab-to-nwb, an open source NWB conversion pipeline including two-photon imaging data from ScanImage, custom ROI segmentation, wheel motion recorded with Spike2, and face motion captured with a CMOS camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Turner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/robert-turner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/robert-turner/</guid>
      <description>We developed turner-lab-to-nwb, an open source NWB conversion pipeline using NeuroConv. The data was of extracellular electrophysiology using a TDT system on non-human primates (NHPs) during a 2-choice reaction time reaching task. The data also included spike sorting using Plexon software and trial events. This data was published as DANDI:000947/0.240510.2211, which contains 1 TB of neurophysiology data, which at the time of publication is the biggest NHP dataset. We also released this electronic notebook to demonstrate how to read and analyze the data directly from the archive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talia Lerner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/talia-lerner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/talia-lerner/</guid>
      <description>We developed lerner-lab-to-nwb, an open source NWB conversion pipeline using NeuroConv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatalystNeuro at Cosyne 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-at-cosyne-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-at-cosyne-2024/</guid>
      <description>This year, CatalystNeuro had the incredible opportunity to be part of the Computational and Systems Neuroscience (Cosyne) 2024 conference, a cornerstone event where the brightest minds in neuroscience converge to explore cutting-edge research and methodologies. Our participation was marked by a fruitful tutorial, engaging discussions, and the invaluable chance to connect with fellow researchers and enthusiasts in the field.&#xA;Workshop on Data Conversion and Publishing One of the highlights of our participation was the workshop led by myself, along with Ryan Ly from Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatalystNeuro at the African Brain Data Science Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/bridging-continents-catalystneuro-at-the-african-brain-data-science-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/bridging-continents-catalystneuro-at-the-african-brain-data-science-academy/</guid>
      <description>At CatalystNeuro, we are passionate about fostering global collaborations that advance the frontiers of neuroscience research and education. Recently, we had the distinct opportunity to contribute to the African Brain Data Science Academy, an initiative under the African Brain Data Network aimed at enhancing data science skills across the continent.&#xA;The Importance of Global Collaboration in Neuroscience In the field of neuroscience, the challenges are as vast as the opportunities. Advancing our understanding of the brain requires not only sophisticated technology but also unparalleled collaboration across borders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatalystNeuro Company Retreat in Barcelona</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-company-retreat-in-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/catalystneuro-company-retreat-in-barcelona/</guid>
      <description>Embracing Work and Play at Villa Mas Sant Jordi In the heart of the Costa Brava, just a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw from the bustling city of Barcelona and the serene beaches of the Mediterranean, CatalystNeuro recently found a perfect fusion of work and relaxation at Villa Mas Sant Jordi. Our annual company retreat was not only a chance to bond and brainstorm but also to immerse ourselves in the splendor of Spanish culture and nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/column/scgb-and-scpab-nwb-adoption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/column/scgb-and-scpab-nwb-adoption/</guid>
      <description>CatalystNeuro has been working with labs in the Simons Collaboration on the Global Brain (SCGB) for 5 years, and the Simons Foundation Plasticity and the Aging Brain for 2 years. In this project, we work with neurophysiology labs that are supported by these collaborations, helping them build custom pipelines to standardize and publish their data, and to integrate NWB into the lab&amp;rsquo;s analysis tools. This project has provided the opportunity to work with a large number of influential neurophysiology research groups from some of the leading research institutes in the United States:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mission/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Solution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/software-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/software-solution/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work with Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work-with-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
